The first thing sold online was a CD. It sold in 1994 for $12.48.
网上售出的第一件商品是一张CD，1994年以12.48美元的价格成交。
In 1995, Amazon launched its online bookshop, and later that year the online auction site that would become eBay sold its first item.
1995年，亚马逊推出了其网上书店，同年晚些时候，后来成为易贝（eBay）的在线拍卖网站售出了第一件商品。
Fast-forward to the modern day and online shopping is huge business.
快进到现在，网购已成为一门庞大的生意。
In contrast to the recent UK announcements that many high-profile retail chains and department stores need to close retail outlets to save money, online shopping is thriving.
近期英国有多家知名零售连锁店和百货公司宣布需关闭实体店以节省开支，与之形成鲜明对比的是，网购正蓬勃发展。
In fact, the UK Office for National Statistics reported that growth in online sales has continued "year-on-year" and stands at just under 20% in April 2018.
事实上，英国国家统计局报告称，网上销售额“逐年”持续增长，2018年4月的增幅略低于20%。
But why?
但这背后的原因是什么？
Maybe it's the convenience.
或许是因为便利。
Online shopping allows you to find what you need from the comfort of your own home.
网购让你足不出户就能找到所需商品。
Then there's the variety.
其次是种类丰富。
The discerning shopper is able to select from a wide range of products from all over the world – whereas physical shops suffer from a more limited choice.
有眼光的购物者能从全球范围内的海量商品中挑选——而实体店的选择则相对有限。
Better yet, with more sophisticated search parameters available, consumers are now better able to specify exactly what they want, and in some cases, even modify products to create bespoke items.
更棒的是，借助更先进的搜索参数，消费者现在能更精准地明确自己的需求，在某些情况下，甚至还能修改产品以打造定制款商品。
Online companies are getting better at targeted advertising too.
网络公司在定向广告方面也做得越来越出色。
Our browsing history and prior purchases are run through algorithms, which generate advertisements that more closely link consumers to the products companies believe we would like to buy.
我们的浏览历史和以往购买记录会通过算法进行分析，从而生成更精准的广告，将消费者与公司认为我们可能想买的产品紧密关联起来。
And since these products are not physically on display in a shop, the company saves money on overheads like rent and electricity. This allows them offer their products at a more reasonable price.
而且，由于这些产品无需在实体店陈列，公司能节省租金、电费等管理费用，这使得它们能以更合理的价格出售商品。
Then there's the reassurance.
此外还有保障措施。
These days, the majority of online retailers offer a safe, convenient returns policy, often at no shipping cost to the buyer – just print out the returns label, affix it to the packaging the item was sent in and receive a full refund.
如今，大多数网络零售商都提供安全便捷的退货政策，通常买家无需支付运费——只需打印退货标签，贴在商品原包装上，就能获得全额退款。
Not only that, but hassle-free complaints procedures and policies mean that if your item is damaged, incorrect or even unwanted, the company can be easily notified and action taken.
不仅如此，简单便捷的投诉流程和政策意味着，若商品受损、发错货甚至只是不想要了，你都能轻松通知公司并获得处理。
Many people still enjoy the experience of buying in a real shop.
仍有很多人喜欢在实体店购物的体验。
The dialogue and customer service received from staff and special events that may be taking place in store can be big pulls.
店员提供的沟通服务和客户支持，以及店内可能举办的特别活动，都是很大的吸引力。
However, the "year-on-year" growth in the online retail sector, as observed by the UK Office for National Statistics, seems to imply that online retail is here to stay and will continue to be a major avenue to shopping for many customers.
不过，英国国家统计局观察到的网络零售行业“逐年”增长趋势似乎表明，网购将长期存在，并将继续成为许多消费者的主要购物渠道。